(Yamanaka) I never expected a scout to come.
This is an opportunity. It's a good opportunity for everyone to take revenge.
What do you mean by quitting?
Was Eternal Boys that light for Kakizaki? NOTE Eternal Boys
♬～
(Sanada) “Again”? NOTE Sanada Again
(Fukuko) I brought you a present, yes.
(Imagawa) It's a new song (Asai) Seriously?
(Kakizaki) I'm actually timid and uncool.
It can't be uncool, can it?
Come to the last live, you too.
I'll sing "Again"
(Imagawa) It's tough! It's hard! Did you see the news? lotus
(Lotus) Hehehehe hahahaha
｟I'm quitting now｠
I'm quitting my office
Huh?
♬～
Has it already been decided? Yeah, it's a shame though
I have just started consulting with a lawyer regarding bankruptcy proceedings.
To be honest, I was barely managing my business with just Ren's earnings.
(Imagawa) Then, are you going to stop Ren?
I would rather move to a major company than stay here.
I'm sure it's good
I want to support this great opportunity.
(Imagawa) Yes, but...
That's why Manpuku Entertainment is over and Eternal Shonen has disbanded.
I have no choice but to cancel the live concert I had planned.
Everyone, please find a new job as soon as possible.
(Ishida) I don't like it.
Isn't it okay? please
I don't want to give up. I don't want to give up either.
please
I'm really sorry
There's nothing I can do now
♬～
Are you really giving up this easily?
ah?
No. Isn't it so easy to find the next one?
I guess it can't be helped...
The old man has gotten better at not giving up.
I don't like it
I don't want to give up yet
♬～
(Sound of door opening and closing)
(sigh)
(Ishida) He's not coming, everyone.
(Imagawa) I guess we should start first.
(Ishida) After all, I'm going home too.
I will resume my part-time job at the cram school tomorrow.
Eh... (Ishida) Then go first.
Hey…
Well, let's practice just the two of us.
(Imagawa) Ah
Come to think of it, Mr. Imagawa, today is the day of distribution, right?
What are you doing?
Ah... sorry
I have some business to do this evening.
What? Business?
Does someone you know want to join a theater company? That's it
So what about Eternal Boy?
No, I want to continue.
As expected, there's nothing I can do this time.
sorry…
(Asai) Actually, I'll be at Kaoru's school starting next week.
I'm a soccer school teacher, so I don't have a part-time job anymore...
That's good (Asai) I'm sorry.
I guess I'm going back to being a regular host now, too?
Ah, what are you going to do about today's broadcast? What?
Eh, it's broadcasting. Today's duty is me and Mr. Yamanaka.
Are you still doing it?
Sanada: Have you found a new job?
No... Are you looking for it properly?
If that's the case, I'll ask President Fukuko to do it.
I am also being introduced by the president...
Why…
Why do people give up so easily?
It can't be helped, but...
but…
nevertheless…
bad
♬～
♬ (Child) If you are happy, clap your hands (clap)
Dad can sing too.
Then let's go together...
♬ (2 people) If you are happy, clap your hands (clap)
♬(2 people) If we're happy, we'll show it with our attitude.
♬Come on, let's all clap our hands
Sanada's trouble consultation room!
(applause)
Today I received messages from everyone.
I will answer your concerns
So without further ado...
"It's hard to be told at work that this is a job that anyone can do."
"What would you do, Sanada-san?"
Hmm... then you should try it.
I wish I could say it, but at times like this
Actually, I can't say it.
I was often told that too.
But I'm sure somewhere
There are people who understand you
We just haven't met yet
I'm sure there will be an encounter that will reward everything I've done up until now.
Everyone has one too.
Thank you for your comment
Sorry I'm alone
No, that's right, I can't do it alone.
There must be six eternal boys.
(sob)
sorry
I feel like who benefits from the old man's tears?
I don't even want to be an idol, I can become one.
I've never thought about it
Just go back to how it was before
But still...
I don't want to break up
Still more...
I want to be an idol with everyone
(sob)
I have to be a forever boy.
I don't want to give up yet
(Kakizaki) Let's do it live. I want to sing "Again" with everyone.